https://www.synercon.co/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Synercon.co
Twitter
Sign Up for NewsletterAbout SynerconConni ChristensenContact Us
HomeInsightsSolutionsProducts and Servicesa.k.a.® SoftwareMetadata and TaxonomiesMethodologiesTrainingResourcesFree a.k.a.® trial
Select Page
IntroductionYour privacy is important to the us. Our goal is to provide you with a personalized online experience that provides you with the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you.Sites covered by this Privacy PolicyThe Synercon Group (Synercon) is a global organisation with affiliated and subsidiary legal entities in various jurisdictions. These include Synercon Management Consulting Pty Ltd, Synercon LLC and Synercon UK Ltd.This Privacy Policy applies to all of Synercon’s web sites, domains, information portals, and registries.Third Party SitesThis website contains links to other sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected at this website. Please be aware that Synercon is not responsible for the privacy practices of third party sites.Information CollectedPersonal InformationSynercon collects personal information from visitors to our website when, for example, you fill out a contact form, subscribe to a mailing lists, provide feedback, or register to obtain a service from us. This is personal information directly communicated by you to Synercon and allows us to provide a service to you.The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs and passwords.Aggregate InformationSynercon may gather aggregate information, which refers to information your computer automatically provides to us and that cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include referral data (the web sites you visited just before and just after our site), the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. For example, when you request a page from one of our sites, our servers log your IP address to create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns and for purposes of system administration.Log FilesEvery time you request or download a file from the web site, Synercon may store data about these events and your IP address in a log file. Synercon may use this information to analyze trends, administer the web site, track users’ movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use or for other business purposes.CookiesOur site may use a feature of your browser to set a “cookie” on your computer. Cookies are small packets of information that a web site’s computer stores on your computer. Synercon’s web sites can then read the cookies whenever you visit our site. We may use cookies in a number of ways, such as to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, to deliver content specific to your interests and to track the pages you’ve visited. These cookies allow us to use the information we collect to customize your experience so that your visit to our site is as relevant and as valuable to you as possible.Most browser software can be set up to deal with cookies. You may modify your browser preference to provide you with choices relating to cookies. You have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, certain of the functions and conveniences of our web site may not work properly, and you may be unable to use those of Synercon’s services that require registration in order to participate, or you will have to re-register each time you visit our site. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the “Help” section of the toolbar. We do not link non-personal information from cookies to personally identifiable information without your permission.How We Use Your InformationThis information will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it. It will not be added to a mailing list or used for any other purpose without your consent.Synercon uses your automatically generated information for statistical analysis purposes to determine the popularity and common use of this website, analyse trends, administer the site, and to track any unauthorised or damaging visits which may cause risk to the operation of the website.Information SharingSynercon does not sell, rent, or lease any individual’s personal information or lists of email addresses to anyone for marketing purposes, and we take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of this information.SecuritySynercon make every effort to protect personal information by users of the web site, including using firewalls and other security measures on its servers. No server, however, is 100% secure, and you should take this into account when submitting personal or confidential information about yourself on any web site, including this one.Changes to this privacy policySynercon may edit this policy from time to time.Follow Us
Twitter
YouTube
LinkedIn
Find out aboutAutoclassification Automation Business Classification Scheme Classification Controlled vocabularies Cross Functional Training Data governance Data models Data quality Digital transition DIRKS Entity Relationship Models Faceted classification File Plan Information governance ISO 15489 Linked data Metadata Ontology Process Improvement Recordkeeping Search System design Taxonomy Thesaurus
Synercon Management Consulting Pty LtdAustralasiaOffice 4
Suite 15/103 George St
Parramatta, NSW 2150
Sydney, AustraliaEuropeSuite 15310
Lower Ground Floor
145-157 St. John Street
London EC1V 4PWNorth America11766 Wilshire Blvd,
Privacy PolicyRead our Privacy PolicyFind out more aboutAggregation
